Standby.
We'll begin preliminary interviews
for Romantic Trip.
Slate.
I'm still not sure
who I'll be traveling with yet.
They've refused to tell me anything.
Yeah, I'm really curious about who it is,
but that's what makes me
anticipate this trip even more,
meeting a foreigner
who doesn't speak your language.
An attractive person at that.
And traveling with them
in an unfamiliar country is quite unusual.
It feels like I'm in a movie
or novel 'cause it's incredible, you know?
I'm a bit nervous and, well, excited.
Wow! I'll be meeting her soon.
I hope she's not disappointed by me.
I hope it'll be a wonderful trip.
This is who you'll be traveling with.
You're telling me right now?
Here. Get ready. You'll find that scene…
-I'm nervous.
-Just play it.
Hello.
I'm Kurosawa Hiro, an actor from Japan.
I'll see you in Canada.
Ah, a familiar face.
I've run into him at a film festival.
Uh, hi.
This is your South Korean travel friend.
My name is Cha Mu-hee.
Uh…
Do Ra-mi.
Am I right?
I see.
Do Ra-mi.
I look forward to Canada!
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?
CANADA
-I'm in room 203.
-I see.
Could you provide the key?
Wow. So nice.
I wonder.
Mu-hee is gonna be staying here?
It's the same place as the crew?
We should put her in a nice hotel.
Like the one Hiro is staying in.
Ms. Cha prefers to stay here.
It's more convenient.
Really? Why?
We don't have anything to shoot here.
What?
Well, if Mu-hee just wants to show us
that she can get along with the crew
and be down to earth, I think
she'd still be better off in a good hotel.
She doesn't need to stay here.
No, she's still nervous
and likes to hang out with the crew.
People she's more comfortable with.
So she's the type who goes to LA
but won't ever leave the hotel room?
I'm like that too.
It's so nice to have her close.
And it'll be easier for meetings.
I feel like it could be a nuisance.
We're already babysitting a crew.
Are we supposed to wait on an actress too?
I'm gonna be looking after her,
so don't be worried.
I have tons of Korean snacks,
like, um, instant noodles.
If you want any, I'd share them with you.
-Ta-da!
-Wow! That's so much!
Wow!
Did you rob a convenience store?
-Are you gonna eat all this?
-Yes. This is Korean soul food.
Please, Producer Park,
take as much as you want. Hmm?
Uh…
If you insist. Here.
Yong-u, you can share this room
with Mr. Joo. It's the biggest one.
Did you bring Neoguri, the spicy ramen?
Oh. It's next on the list!
Rewatching this
shows how out of it I was that day.
I wouldn't have been able to recognize
him at the after-party.
I found out his nickname in Japan
is "Prince Charming."
Let's make his heart beat so fast
he dies of an attack.
Don't say that kind of thing.
Do Ra-mi has killed so many people.
It's an image I wanna erase.
No, don't… …kill him like this.
Kill him like that.
Oh!
Like this?
No. Let's go for something more natural.
You'll be an innocent female lead
in a Japanese… coming-of-age story?
Ah! Got it!
Hiro dear?
Oh wow! You can do anything!
Good, then.
I'll act my heart out. Be natural.
By the way, do you know
if Hiro is in Canada yet?
Hmm. He could be here.
Should I reach out to Mr. Joo?
He's coming with them.
Joo Ho-jin?
No, it's fine.
If you call him,
he'll think I told you to.
Yeah, let's not.
It'll hurt my self-respect too.
All right, take it easy.
I'm close by, so shout if you need me.
Hey!
You're sharing a room with Joo Ho-jin?
Which means he'll be
close by as well, right?
Stop that! Get your mind off him.
Set your sights on Hiro!
Yes!
That's right. Focus on Hiro.
Joo Ho-jin's here for work.
In any case,
we're here together on this adventure.
It's freezing.
Sorry about that.
Uh, Mr. Joo, do you mind
if we have a brief chat?
Go, grab his bags.
Mm.
We almost didn't make it to Canada.
It's thanks to you,
we could coax him into coming, Mr. Joo.
I just interpreted, Mr. Kim.
It's you who did the coaxing.
He wanted us to cast from the short list,
but we picked Do Ra-mi instead,
and, well, he was shocked.
Her public image is a horror queen.
Ms. Cha Mu-hee's casting wasn't discussed
with Hiro or his team at all?
We talked with his agency.
Do Ra-mi's global fame would benefit
their Japanese actor, so they agreed.
But, well… …it's good
the crew doesn't speak Japanese
because only you and I would know
how he feels about her
and about this unfortunate situation.
Mr. Kim, are you trying
to cover this up? Is that it?
This show is about them dating.
The premise is a fairy tale.
Who do you know who would wanna be
with a guy who says he's not interested?
-She would never like him. You agree?
-Yes, that's true.
Telling her would only
compromise the romance.
Do you wanna get
in the way of their romance?
I don't.
Then we must keep this our secret
between you and me, you know?
You can't mention this to her,
even if… you're friends.
I don't gossip,
including when I'm interpreting.
And thankfully,
Do Ra-mi doesn't know Japanese.
Hiro may cross the line
and say something rude,
so please filter that out for her.
On-the-spot editing.
Since I'm the, um, producer in charge,
I'm asking you to edit, okay? Hmm?
No, I won't.
An interpreter translates words
as they're said.
The editing? That will be done by you.
I ask this of you
since Do Ra-mi and you are buddies.
Why do you call her Do Ra-mi?
Everyone calls her Do Ra-mi
when I translate.
Her name is Cha Mu-hee.
We know.
But Do Ra-mi is the celebrity here,
and that name's much catchier.
When you call someone the wrong name,
it makes the job harder.
Please refer to her as Cha Mu-hee.
Fine.
Hey, welcome.
-You're here too.
-I am.
Thank you.
I'm staying in the smaller room.
You can have the bigger one.
Really? Thanks.
Wow.
What's this stuff?
Yummy snacks. Have some if you want.
Everything from instant noodles
to the latest.
You'll like this. It's new.
I had to line up at the store for it.
Huh.
Strawberry flavor?
You met up with Hiro? How is he?
I bet he's really excited
to work with Mu-hee on this?
How's Cha Mu-hee?
She excited to work with Hiro?
She's super thrilled.
He's a good-looking guy.
He's supposed to be sweet and considerate.
Mm.
So Mu-hee thinks
Hiro's image is nice, yeah?
Yes, she does.
The two of them
had seen each other before.
He was kind to Mu-hee
and treated her well.
He was kind?
They've been sort of into each other
since the show was announced.
Oh. Of course.
Cha Mu-hee thinks
that Hiro's into her, then.
Joo Ho-jin was interested?
It's just 'cause you asked
a bunch of questions.
I didn't.
I just asked him about Hiro,
and he kept pushing
and… wanted to know if you liked Hiro.
Really?
So tell me what you said.
I said you both already knew each other
and liked one another.
When I told him that, he looked…
-What? Come on!
-Hmm…
I'm not sure if it's accurate
to say he looked… upset by the situation
or worried, maybe? I don't know.
Whoa. Why would he act like this?
Why would it worry him
that I may be into Hiro?
Okay, stop. You're being delusional.
How was the meeting today? It went well?
Well… So the producer suggested
I could plan a surprise for him,
so I told them that
I'd come up with something fun.
A surprise that's fun?
I like it. We'll come up with a good one.
Ah, Yong-u.
-Could you come here for a sec?
-Sure.
-Mu-hee, go get some rest.
-Mm.
Yeah, I just wanted to check in
to make sure
everything is good for tomorrow.
Yong-u.
Are you there?
Just a moment.
Oh my! Joo Ho-jin?
Isn't Yong-u staying here?
Oh?
Yes. I… I share this room with him.
Okay, is that so?
I came by to see Yong-u.
My room's right there.
It's just across the hallway.
Yes, I know. I planned to come say hi.
You did?
Yong-u mentioned you left your phone here,
and he's hanging on to it.
I was just talking to him.
This is Yong-u.
Go ahead. It's him.
Yes, Yong-u.
Mu-hee, I heard everything.
What's wrong with you?
Yeah, okay. Well, glad it's all good.
Well done. You've found Yong-u so quickly,
and there's no reason
for me to go to your room, so…
so what now?
I used him as a lame excuse.
I worried if I came
to see you by yourself,
you might feel intimidated,
and, uh, you might freak out a bit.
Oh. I'm terrified.
I came here to say something else.
Um, forget it. Good night.
Let's walk. We'll talk outside.
Or we could just… stay and talk in there.
I'm sorry. I can't invite you in.
I'm too terrified.
What if I die?
What did you eat on the plane?
I had mushrooms with rice.
Your flight came in from Japan,
so did they have sushi or donburi?
Maybe tempura.
It means deep-fried food
in Japanese, right?
Tempura does mean deep-fried food,
but I got donburi.
If you're saying things
off the top of your head
just to make conversation,
can we start with how we're doing?
So…
how are you?
Great. But busy, you know.
And you?
Hey!
Any news regarding her wedding?
It's still happening next week.
I've used this
as my way of not attending it.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll be pretty busy working anyway.
Next week will be gone in a blur.
Hmm.
Uh…
Do Ra-mi, is she still, um, haunting you?
She isn't fully gone.
I think a little about her,
how she's similar to comments online.
Comments?
The hateful, mean ones.
"Do you think these good times will last?"
And when it gets bad, she says,
"Serves you right."
"I knew this would happen."
She's like an online troll.
I wanna sue her.
She lives here, so I can't do that.
I can just pretend to ignore her.
If she's up there, as you've mentioned,
then that means you're making
those hateful comments up yourself.
Oh, yeah? Am I?
Right. I guess.
Tell me everything about these comments.
What does Do Ra-mi say to you?
Word for word.
We've ended up here together.
You're so giddy
after making him work here
to see the Northern Lights as an excuse.
He's the bachelor next door.
He's sleeping close by, so you'll see him
every day as you keep hoping,
while working and… eating together.
Why would I tell you that kind of stuff?
I'm the one who knows about it.
You've asked me for help. So tell me.
If everything Do Ra-mi says is up here,
you want me to share that?
It would be like
letting you read my diary.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Is there a translator in your entries?
I don't know.
How can you say you don't know?
Is it full of insults about me?
You think it's just insults?
Do Ra-mi has great insights.
If you only knew, you'd be frightened
to be alone with me tonight.
Why is that? Why?
You scaredy-cat.
Hiro?
What is it?
Why are you here?
I was waiting to tell you
about tomorrow's shoot.
Are you all right?
What's that?
The hotel sent a welcome cake and flowers.
Want some?
Ever seen me eat anything at night?
A slice of shortcake has 600 calories.
That'd be two hours on the treadmill.
Why is it so cold here this time of year?
I told you many times that Canada's fall
is colder than Japan's winter.
-Shall I turn up the heater?
-No, then it'll get too dry.
My eyes are already so dry
that they might pop out any minute.
What do you need to tell me?
Uh, they're asking if you prepared
a surprise gift for your first meeting.
Not likely.
Are they asking
because she's prepared something?
I believe so.
Fine. Then tell them
I'll prepare something too.
I guess I'll party with the zombie.
Are you still mad she didn't recognize you
that night and taking it out on her?
Sure, she was rude,
but do I look like a jerk
who'd hold such a petty grudge?
I asked you a question.
Why aren't you answering me?
Fine, I'll take your word for it.
I just don't like her public image.
You hate Do Ra-mi's zombie image
that much?
Prince Hiro, who'd smile like the sun,
even before a zombie.
That's the image I hate.
Have a bite of something sweet.
It'll make you feel better.
I'll leave it here.
Hearts, huh?
Come on.
Tell me all the things
Hiro has said about me.
Why ask the interpreter?
Go and talk to the director.
When someone goes on a blind date,
it's normal to ask questions.
Well, what…
Why would this shoot count as a date?
It's a shoot, but it's still a date.
And the person connecting us,
in this case, is you, Joo Ho-jin.
You're… the true messenger of love.
So what did he say?
That's all the more reason
not to say anything.
I don't wanna say anything
to muddy the waters here.
Well, why did you get upset, then?
Just tell me what he said.
Who's upset?
Yong-u said you were.
That you were sad when I said
I was into Hiro, romantically.
Yong-u may have misheard.
You understand?
The translator must never interpret
with a bias.
It might lead to silly misunderstandings
like this one.
So tell me, Joo Ho-jin,
you can interpret
with no emotions whatsoever?
If we act cutesy and adorable
with one another, it won't get to you?
My work is to be a listener
and translate between the two languages.
What's said or done involves
no emotions or reactions on my part.
Oh, what a relief.
That's good 'cause I worried about
crossing the line and embarrassing you.
Now I'm reassured
I can act cheesy and lovey-dovey.
Wait, why would I be embarrassed?
Oh, the drama.
From now on, go ask the producer
if you have any questions.
They wanna make the show dramatic
by all means.
They'll say anything.
You're closer to me. I can trust you.
I'm asking you to be on my side.
They're pretty.
I'm gonna make a heart with these leaves.
Like what they do on socials.
I'll make one that says,
"I'm giving you this heart
to celebrate our first meeting."
How do you say "heart" in Japanese?
"Heart" is "ha-to" in Japanese.
Of course.
Hearts are universal. Amazing.
You've made me think…
about things people said.
I think you're right.
The hateful comments are only my thoughts.
I told you that
this is my long-awaited festival?
Hmm.
What if all the fireworks will end
and everyone will go away?
I'll end up all by myself again, I'm sure.
I'm
gonna be left with nothing.
That's why Do Ra-mi's here
and leaves comments like,
"What a sad loser. You're going to fail."
You shouldn't listen to Do Ra-mi.
It won't happen to you
as long as you don't let it.
If you say so.
I said I'll help you,
but I don't know what more I can do.
I can neither hear nor see Do Ra-mi
because she lives inside your head.
You said you'd root for me, didn't you?
You said you'd never ask me out,
but you'd keep rooting.
Do that. You're good at it.
Plus, you're basically
the only one who knows
about the hateful troll in my head.
Go on!
Keep rooting for me like you do.
Pray I never lose to Do Ra-mi.
Yay, Cha Mu-hee.
Win. Keep winning.
Go Cha Mu-hee!
Let's figure out a better cheer.
Cha Mu-hee.
May I…
Mu-hee!
Yong-u will think
I was flirting with you again.
I'm going inside.
Good night, bachelor next door.
-Do you have my phone?
-Ho-jin--
I have it right here. Were you…
I was just asking about Hiro.
Of course you were.
Producer Kim.
Why didn't he take his walkie-talkie?
Oh, hi! Well…
You… need to go over there.
Mu-hee!
You look so pretty this morning.
-How are you today?
-I'm excited.
Good. As for the cameras,
we'll make them
as unintrusive as possible.
And, oh,
we watch everything from the monitors
in our video village over there.
That's the main one.
You'll hear the interpreter
through your earpiece.
Sir, in today's script…
Could you lower the drone
to focus on Ms. Cha Mu-hee?
Good.
That camera could readjust…
Should we switch from the drone
with this shot? It's more dynamic.
-Switch these two?
-Yeah, yeah.
Can you hear me, Mr. Joo?
I can hear you.
Fun. I can hear you too.
Done. It's in.
The weather is so perfect.
All right, cameras, at your positions.
Drone, follow Hiro.
Let's begin the first day
of Romantic Trip.
Let's do this.
Move the drone towards Cha Mu-hee.
Let's follow Hiro now.
Nice to meet you.
Oh.
Yes, hello.
I'm headed your way.
Well, I'm sitting
right under a big maple tree.
Will you be able to find me?
I see you're sitting on a bench.
Yes, I am. Good.
You can see me?
Where are you?
Why don't you come find me?
Sorry?
It wouldn't be any fun
if I just appeared in front of you.
Try to find me.
Ah. Well, it's a huge park.
I don't know where to start.
Take a good look around.
You'll find me below the red balloon.
He's under a red balloon?
A red balloon!
I see the balloon!
Then, um, I'll head over that way.
Wow. Hiro's created
an interesting situation on his own.
It's pretty entertaining.
Who knew Do Ra-mi could run.
Drone, keep your sights on Ms. Cha Mu-hee.
Follow her.
Whoa!
Ay!
Okay.
Next is a blue balloon.
Run!
A blue balloon this time.
Okay…
Oh my. You're really making this hard.
Wait right there. I'll go and find you.
Look straight to your left.
He's on your left.
Yes!
I caught you!
She found him! She got him!
Well done, Do Ra-mi! Good work.
-She did it!
-Nice, Do Ra-mi!
She's pretty and smart. Wow.
We had zero reasons to be worried.
They're entertaining.
This is what's entertaining?
Making someone run around a huge area?
It's a reality show.
We've met recently, you know?
I didn't get your name then.
Mr. Hiro Kurosawa. Is that right?
I remember you too.
So we meet again, Ms. Cha Mu-hee.
Wow, I might have run around everywhere
until all of those balloons were gone.
I'm glad you found me
before they were all gone.
I got these as a present for you.
Ah!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I didn't catch it and lost your gift.
It's fine. I had fun thanks to you.
Thinking back
to how you were in that movie,
I thought running around like crazy
to find a guy
would suit you better
than sitting prettily waiting for him.
And I was right.
Wouldn't it be funny
if we cut from you running just now
to the shot from your movie
of you running with a bloodied axe?
Right?
It was so fun, like shooting a movie,
Ah.
That was kind of fun, yeah.
I had fun too.
Watching you frantically pedal that bike
was pretty hilarious.
Ah! I have a present for you too.
Huh.
This is my present.
It's a heart.
This is the worst.
-Oh my.
-Oh!
They make such a pretty picture.
They're both "wow."
Couldn't look better.
Canada is the country of maple leaves.
I made a maple leaf heart
that symbolizes that.
Here you go.
Is something wrong?
There's dust in my eye.
My contact fell out.
He says he can't continue filming
without his contacts.
He didn't bring any of his spares.
New ones can be shipped,
but they'll get here tomorrow evening.
So we stop filming
until the lenses arrive?
What?
This afternoon,
we planned to go to Horseshoe Canyon.
Today's the only day we can film there.
I'm so sorry.
I'm very sorry.
Wait. Oh, Nanami…
Do something about this.
It's my fault.
Sorry for… for that pile of leaves.
It's fine. It's okay.
We're supposed to find
a contact lens in here?
If we find it, would it be wearable?
Keep an eye out for something shiny.
Be careful. It's small.
What am I doing?
"This is the worst."
I heard him say that.
Although no one else was able to hear him.
If that's what you heard him say…
why didn't you translate
what you actually heard?
I'd ruin this project.
Now, I need your help.
We have to resolve this matter
quickly and quietly.
I'll do my best too.
There's one thing
Hiro is obsessed with right now.
That might resolve things.
Honestly. Does it have to come to this?
What a day.
Everyone's blaming Mu-hee
for holding up the shoot.
They say the heart made of leaves
was a bad idea.
Why would his contact fall out?
And why was it so damn windy?
Where are you going?
Just to meet my friend downtown.
Wow, everyone likes this guy.
Joo Ho-jin, I heard you're going downtown.
Can you give me a ride?
I gotta go somewhere.
You didn't wait
to hear yes or no, did you?
Where you off to?
A good Japanese restaurant.
Why go to a Japanese one in Canada?
I wanna pick up takeout
for a Japanese friend.
Let's just go.
There's supposed to be a very famous
Japanese restaurant here,
and when you're away,
you miss food from back home.
He's been here for two days.
I doubt he misses it already.
We had Japanese food on the flight too.
I can't apologize to him empty-handed.
Why see him at all
when you don't understand each other?
Nanami, his assistant? She speaks English.
I have to ask him to continue
with glasses on or something else.
Production's responsible for that.
Don't go see him.
Why don't you want me to go?
Does he not like me?
Is that what you think?
When we were shooting this morning,
Hiro was saying a whole lot,
but you only said a brief sentence
and moved on.
What did he say to me?
I don't know. I can't remember.
I translated every single word.
Don't you have somewhere to go?
Just go now. I will be okay.
You're seeing a friend, right?
I'll be right back. Be right here.
Don't see him alone, okay?
I wonder if that part
he didn't translate was rude.
These were really hard to get.
-Thank you.
-Hmm.
These were really hard to get as well.
Oh.
Honestly, I would've done
anything for this.
Thank you.
He seems to be okay.
That guy is just a big liar!
What should we do?
Take it.
You can crush his skull.
Throw it at him!
Don't be a pushover!
He took off.
This time,
Do Ra-mi put a rock in my hand.
She said, "Throw it."
But if I…
If I smacked him right now,
it would make things worse
and maybe ruin the whole show.
I held myself back.
That means you won.
You said you're rooting for me?
Then tell me everything you know.
Why is he mocking me like this?
There were problems
before we even got here.
He didn't want you cast
as his partner.
Ah.
So he just doesn't like me.
Joo Ho-jin.
You already knew he didn't like me at all?
You just listened while
I was being teased on TV yesterday.
How silly and stupid I looked when I said
I was going to be all cutesy?
You don't have to hold it in. Get angry.
You should have talked me out
of making that stupid heart.
It really was that zombie.
Why did she just walk away?
She definitely saw me.
The interpreter is here to see you.
The interpreter? Why?
I bet the production crew sent you
to convince me to resume the shoot.
Your eyesight must be quite poor.
Those glasses look very thick.
It's an insecurity of mine.
I don't even leave my house
without my contacts.
So I can't continue the shoot.
I see.
Well, that's a shame.
Hiro.
I suggest you check again thoroughly
whether you really didn't bring
any spare contacts.
Otherwise,
you may really regret it.
Ah…
Hiro will be able to start
shooting again now.
-Oh.
-That's great.
Wow, Mr. Joo must've been able
to persuade him.
He was able to find some
spare contacts in his bag.
I'm sorry for any inconvenience.
It's not a problem.
I'm glad it's worked out. Let's go.
-We'll be going again.
-Oh.
He would like to talk to you
to clear the air
before resuming production,
if that's okay.
Both of you.
Let's go.
Keep in mind
I'm never gonna
Leave your life ever long…
You'll be okay…
Thank you so much!
-I love you!
-Will you sign my shirt?
-Sure.
-Oh!
Your name?
So babe, I promise
Forever I'll never leave…
Thank you so much!
-Bye!
-Thank you!
Forever I'll never leave
Did you turn your phone off, Mu-hee?
Were you looking for me?
Why? So you can make fun of me?
The shoot they canceled is on again.
We have to hurry and get over there.
Was Hiro embarrassed
that I saw him at the clock?
Was he afraid
that I would tell production?
What made him change his mind?
Who knows.
In any case,
it's good that we're shooting today.
So then what are you gonna do, Mu-hee?
Can you pretend you don't know?
Of course. I've often had to pretend
in front of people who don't like me.
If I didn't hide my feelings, I'd lose.
You translated for me
at the doctor's office.
You know I grew up with relatives that
didn't welcome me. I adapted to survive.
What is it?
I've taken my share of abuse,
so don't worry. I'll be fine.
You said Do Ra-mi put a rock in your hand?
Even if you can't throw it,
tell him that you have it.
That way, he won't treat you…
He won't treat you badly anymore.
If you feel like telling him,
I'll translate it exactly for you.
You mean it?
No matter… if I swear or not?
You said you don't translate profanity.
Swear at him. Sure.
I'll interpret everything.
You didn't interpret what he said earlier
on purpose. Why not?
Were you worried I'd get too upset
and ruin the shoot?
I guess you feel bad for agreeing
to trick me with Producer Kim.
That's not it.
Who wants to translate that?
It, uh… upset me for a reason.
I thought no matter what,
your job was to avoid emotions
and interpret everything whatsoever.
I said that. Guess I've changed my mind,
and now I'm on your side.
I'm sorry.
Well, if you're on my side,
I'll forgive you.
You make me feel all right
You make me feel…
-Go ahead so you can get ready.
-See you or hear you soon.
Joo Ho-jin.
Thank you!
When I look into your eyes
Fall in love with you…
If they meet over there…
Sorry we're late.
-Oh, yes, great.
-Sorry.
-Sorry, sorry.
-Go to your mark.
Sorry.
Sorry. I'm here. Hi. Hello.
This place is huge.
How many Tokyo Domes would fit in here?
The clock tower.
See? It's a heart.
The last one was ruined.
Let's be good to this one, right?
The birds are flying…
We're ready to start shooting
at Horseshoe Canyon.
Something they want to imply
I greet the breeze
And nod to the trees
I heard the winds reply
A thousand languages start to whisper
Around my world
One quiet voice answers them
In gentle word…
You don't even say thanks?
Stuck in my throat
Round and round
I wanna speak out…
This is breathtaking.
Echoes of my voice answer alone…
Wow!
Tell me the truth
What don't I see?
Stuck in my thoughts
I walk till I fade
I feel the love…
This is great.
We'll be able to wrap this up
before sunset.
Look at that.
Why is she in such a good mood?
Round and round, my life just goes on
I greet the breeze
-And nod to the trees…
-Oh.
I hear the winds…
Those words I don't need to translate.
Hey.
How did Mr. Joo get Hiro
to come back again?
I've visited Canada before.
Vancouver, Calgary, Banff.
He's obsessed
with attending sporting events.
He's been to Canada a few times,
but he's been sad about never being able
to go to an ice hockey game.
Ice hockey.
I'm guessing you'd need
your contacts to watch the hockey game.
Hey, Yong-u.
Where are the snacks you packed?
You said you had a bunch of chips.
Yeah, I'm sure I did.
I had a bag full of stuff.
Why have… This is all I have left?
Where… where's my stuff?
Thank you for the ticket.
-You helped me out, Robin.
-No. Thank you!
Their favorite K-pop band had these,
but they're impossible to get in Canada.
Thanks to you,
I scored some serious brownie points
with these girls.
-What do you say to him?
-Thank you! You're the best!
Exactly. Thank you, Ho-jin.
You seem a lot better
after getting those tickets.
To be honest,
when he told you to talk with the crew
instead of taking it out on Cha Mu-hee,
I was certain you'd get mad.
I was waiting for a chance to score
when Mr. Joo gave me… the perfect assist.
It wasn't just because of the ticket.
Thanks to him,
the crew agreed to accept my input.
We're here to create
a reality television show.
We don't want you to smile in a fake way
like you're some kind of prince, you know?
When you're in a bad mood
or if there's something
you'd rather not do,
tell us, be honest.
Then what if I never warm up
to Ms. Cha Mu-hee
and decide I don't want
to keep traveling with her?
Would that be okay?
Yes.
Well, we'd just have
you travel separately. That's it.
But it's possible
you will start to actually like her.
You could grow fond of her, you know.
Would you admit to it if it was the case?
That's ridiculous.
If I grow to like Ms. Cha Mu-hee…
I won't hide it. I'll confess my feelings.
This isn't a joke. I mean it.
So please translate my words verbatim.
I didn't wanna translate it.
It was wrong. For some reason, it hurt.
The heart of a zombie…
Have I been infected?
CAN THIS LOVE BE TRANSLATED?